American Congregational Association records, 1846-2022.
Congregational Library & Archives
- Board of directors records, 1851 2022; 1851-2022; 309 Folders; 8 Volumes
  - Library committee records, 1938 2011; 1901-2011; 45 Folders; 2 Volumes
    - Library committee records, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Library committee records, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Library committee records, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Library committee records, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Library committee records, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Library committee records, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Library committee records, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Library committee records, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Library committee records, 2011 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Executive committee records, 1929 1999; 1929-1999; 34 Folders
    This subseries contains the records of the executive committee of the American Congregational Association. Throughout the course of its history, the executive committee handled most all matters that did not need to go before the full board. After 1998, the executive committee was disbanded and its responsibilities given the numerous, more focused, board committees, to further empower the full board. Many 20th century decisions made by the American Congregational Association can be traced to decisions made by the executive committee. The bulk of the materials in this subseries are meeting minutes.
    - Executive committee records, 1929 1942; 1929-1942 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Executive committee reports, 1938 1977; 1938-1977 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Executive committee records, 1943 1953; 1943-1953 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Executive committee records, 1954 1961; 1954-1961 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Executive committee records, 1962 1970; 1962-1970 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Executive committee meeting minutes, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Investment committee records, 1969 2009; 1969-2009; 13 Folders
    This subseries contains records created by, and for, the investment committee of the American Congregational Association. The investment committee was created to provide board oversight of the investment accounts of the American Congregational Association. The bulk of the records are meeting minutes, though financial and investment records are also a part of the investment committee records.
    - Investment policy, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Investment committee records, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Investment committee records, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Investment committee records, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Investment committee records, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Investment committee records, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Investment committee records, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Investment committee records, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Investment committee records, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Investment committee records, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Investment committee records, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Investment committee records, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Investment committee records, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Treasurer's reports, 1970 1996; 1970-1996; 27 Folders
    This subseries contains reports made by the treasurer of the American Congregational Association to the board of directors. The bulk of the materials within this subseries are quarterly financial reports.
    - Treasurer's reports, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Personnel committee records, 1999 2009; 1999-2009; 7 Cubic Feet
    This subseries contains records created by, and for, the personnel committee of the American Congregational Association. The personnel committee was created to provide board oversight of the employees of the American Congregational Association. The bulk of the records are meeting minutes, though presentations, proposals, and reports to the personnel committee are also included.
    - Personnel committee records, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Personnel committee records, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Personnel committee records, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Personnel committee records, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 87)
    - Personnel committee records, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 88)
    - Personnel committee records, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 89)
    - Personnel committee records, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Board development committee records, 1999 2010; 1999-2010; 12 Folders
    This subseries contains records created by, and for, the board development committee of the American Congregational Association. The board development committee, also sometimes called the nominating committee, was created to recommend new members for the board. The bulk of the records are meeting minutes and communications between board members.
    - Board development committee records, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Board development committee records, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Board development committee records, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Board development committee records, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Board development committee records, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Board development committee records, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Board development committee records, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Board development committee records, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Board development committee records, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Board development committee records, 2008 (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Board development committee records, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Board development committee records, 2010 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Development committee records, 1999 2022; 1999-2022; 11 Folders
    This subseries contains records created by, and for, the development committee of the American Congregational Association. The development committee has had different names throughout its history including the advancement committee, the financial development committee, and the finance development committee. The development committee was created to provide board oversight of the associations fundraising efforts. The bulk of the records are meeting minutes, though presentations, proposals, and reports to the development committee are also included.
    - Finance development committee records, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Finance development committee records, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Finance development committee records, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Finance development committee records, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Financial development committee records, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Financial development committee records, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Advancement committee records, 2016 2017; 2016-2017 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Advancement committee records, 2018 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Advancement committee records, 2019 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Advancement committee records, 2020 2021; 2020-2021 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Development committee records, 2022 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Program committee records, 2000 2008; 2000-2008; 9 Folders
    This subseries contains records created by, and for, the program committee of the American Congregational Association. The program committee was created to provide board oversight of the Library's public programming. The bulk of the records are meeting minutes.
    - Program committee records, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Program committee records, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Program committee records, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Program committee records, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Program committee records, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Program committee records, 2005 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Program committee records, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Program committee records, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Program committee records, 2008 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Building committee records, 2000 2009; 2000-2009; 9 Folders
    This subseries contains records created by, and for, the building committee of the American Congregational Association. The building committee was created to provide board oversight of the management and functions of the Congregational House at 14 Beacon Street, Boston, Massachusetts. The bulk of the records are meeting minutes, though presentations, proposals, and reports to the building committee are also included.
    - Building committee records, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Building committee records, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Building committee records, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Building committee records, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - Building committee records, 2004 (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Building committee records, 2005 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Building committee records, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Building committee records, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Building committee records, 2009 (Box 3, Folder 99)
- Financial records, 1851 2021; 1851-2021; 71 Folders; 30 Volumes
  This series contains records related to the finances of the American Congregational Association. The bulk of the series contains correspondence and ledgers kept by the treasurers of the American Congregational Association. This series also contains records related to membership and pledge drives that were intended to raise money for the association. This series also contains records related to taxes paid and owed by the American Congregational Association.
  - Ledgers and receipts, 1851 2019; 1851-2019; 16 Folders; 25 Volumes
    This subseries contains financial records related to the functions of the American Congregational Association. Most of the account books within this series were kept by the various treasurers of the American Congregational Association. This subseries also contains some records of receipts and disbursements. Financial records more specifically related to the buildings owned by the American Congregational Association and to the Congregational Library & Archives may be found in their respective series.
    - Daybook, 1851 1871; 1851-1871 (Box 5, Volume 2)
    - Daybook, 1871 1887; 1871-1880 (Box 5, Volume 3)
    - Daybook, 1880 1887; 1880-1887 (Box 5, Volume 4)
    - Daybook, 1872 1898; 1872-1898 (Box 5, Volume 5)
    - Daybook, 1891 1900; 1891-1900 (Box 5, Volume 6)
    - Daybook, 1900 1907; 1900-1907 (Box 5, Volume 7)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1853 1872; 1853-1872 (Box 6, Volume 3)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1857-1870 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1870 1872; 1870-1872 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - James P. Melledge ledger, 1871 1872; 1871-1872 (Box 6, Volume 4)
    - Insurance certificates, 1873 1897; 1873-1897 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Agreement to make up deficit, 1874 1875; 1874-1875 (Box 8, Volume 4)
    - National Bank account books, 1877 1886; 1877-1886 (Box 8, Volume 5-6)
    - Daybook, 1907 1912; 1907-1912 (Box 8, Volume 1)
    - Daybook, 1913 1917; 1913-1917 (Box 8, Volume 2)
    - Daybook, 1917 1918; 1917-1918 (Box 8, Volume 3)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1912 1928; 1912-1928 (Box 8, Volume 7)
    - Ledger, 1918 1926; 1918-1926 (Box 11, Volume 1)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1920 1922; 1920-1922 (Box 6, Volume 5)
    - Deposit book, 1922 1924; 1922-1924 (Box 8, Volume 8)
    - Comparative statements of income and expenditures, 1922-1929 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1924 1932; 1924-1932 (Box 8, Volume 9)
    - Ledger, 1926 1933; 1926-1933 (Box 11, Volume 2)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1927-1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1931 1949; 1931-1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1949 1963; 1949-1963 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Receipts and disbursements, 1963 1977; 1963-1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Financial reports, 1932 1995; 1932-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Ledger, 1933 1940; 1933-1940 (Box 11, Volume 3)
    - Investment reports, 1935 1961; 1935-1961 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1952 1961; 1952-1961 (Box 8, Volume 10)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1952 1961; 1952-1961 (Box 8, Volume 11)
    - Treasurer's diary, 1962 1964; 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Assets and funds, 1965 1972; 1965-1972 (Box 6, Volume 6)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1965 1976; 1965-1976 (Box 6, Volume 7)
    - Treasurer's account book, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Financial statements, 1970 1977; 1970-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Tax exemption ledger, 1977 1979; 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Cambridge Trust Company loan, 2002 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Annual reports, 2012 2019; 2012-2019 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Memberships and subscriptions, 1853 2001; 1853-2001; 9 Folders; 5 Volumes
    This subseries contains records which are related to membership programs or subscription drives; both are activities that the American Congregational Association has undertaken to raise funds during the course of its history.
    - Membership list, 1853 1854; 1853-1854 (Box 6, Volume 8)
    - List of members, 1853 1887; 1853-1887 (Box 8, Volume 12)
    - Subscriptions, 1854 1871; 1854-1871 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Membership list, circa 1860 (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Contributions, 1866 1872; 1866-1872 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - List of members and constitution, 1869 1920; 1869-1920 (Box 8, Volume 13)
    - Membership certificates, 1870 1879; circa 1870-1879 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Membership certificates, 1871 1875; 1871-1875 (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - List of life members, 1889 (Box 8, Volume 14)
    - Membership certificates, 1911 (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Dues paid, 1959 1966; 1959-1966 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Pledge books, 1964 1967; 1964-1967 (Box 6, Volume 9)
    - Membership lists, 1980 1999; 1980-1999 (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Membership correspondence, 1981 2001; 1981-2001 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence, 1871 1977; 1871-1977; 22 Folders
    This subseries contains correspondence related to the finances of the Congregational American Association at large. The bulk of the correspondence is related to William Cobb and Ralph Whitney.
    - William Cobb correspondence, 1871 1918; 1871-1918 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - William Cobb correspondence, 1888 1924; 1888-1924 (Box 16, Folder 33-35)
    - William Cobb correspondence, 1898 1902; 1898-1902 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Treasurer's correspondence, 1923 1929; 1923-1929 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Treasurer's correspondence, 1924 1973; 1924-1973 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Treasurer's correspondence, 1925 1931; 1925-1931 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Treasurer's correspondence, 1925 1932; 1925-1932 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, 1930 1939; 1930-1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, 1930 1939; 1930-1939 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, 1930 1939; 1930-1939 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, 1938 1943; 1938-1943 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, 1941 1943; 1941-1943 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, A-B, 1952 1959; 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, C-L, 1952 1959; 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, M, 1952 1959; 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, N-Z, 1952 1959; 1952-1959 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Financial correspondence, 1957 1977; 1957-1977 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, A-B, 1960 1966; 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, G-N, 1960 1966; 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Ralph Whitney correspondence, N-Z, 1960 1966; 1960-1966 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Tax and audit records, 1924 2021; 1924-2021; 24 Folders
    This subseries contains records related to federal, state, and city taxes. Most of the records are related to audited financial records and form 990s but this series also contains records related to tax statuses, tax abatements, and retirement accounts.
    - Tax abatements, 1924-1944 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Tax status, 1924 1978; 1924-1978 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Electrical modernization tax exemption, 1959 1961; 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Audited financial statements, 1969 1979; 1969-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Audited financial statements, 1980 1989; 1980-1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Audited financial statements, 1990 1999; 1990-1999 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Audited financial statements, 2000 2009; 2000-2009 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Audited financial statements, 2010 2018; 2010-2018 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Audited financial statements, 2021 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Retirement program, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Form 990, 1975 1985; 1975-1985 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Form 990, 1993 1999; 1993-1999 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Form 990, 2000 2009; 2000-2009 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Form 990, 2010 2016; 2010-2016 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Tax abatements and real estate taxes, 1983 2005; 1983-2005 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Pension plan, 1987 1988; 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Tax exemptions, 1995 1996; 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Tax, abatement, and audit records, 1996 2001; 1996-2001 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Abatements, 2001 2007; 2001-2007 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Tax status confirmations, 2004 2008; 2004-2008 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Pension plans, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Pension protection act, 2007 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Return of property held for charitable purposes, 2017 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Massachusetts Charities Division filing, 2021 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Building records, 1846 2019; 1846-2019; 165 Folders; 9 Volumes; 9 Boxes
  This series contains records related to the construction, management, maintenance, and history of the buildings owned by the American Congregational Association. The majority of the records within this series relate to the Congregational House at 14 Beacon Street, Boston, Massachusetts, whose construction was completed in 1898, though some of the earliest records relate to the Somerset Building, which housed the Congregational Library before it was moved to the Congregational House in 1898. This series contains correspondence, reports, deeds and quitclaim deeds, financial records, rent books, assessments, construction documents, legal proceedings, and architectural drawings. This series also contains records directly related to the American Congregational Association's decisions on whether to sell the building at various times during the association's history. Records related specifically to the facilities of the library may be found in the series, "Congregational Library & Archives records, 1853-2022."
  - Financial records, 1846 2012; 1846-2012; 10 Folders; 1 Volume
    This subseries contains financial and legal records related to the American Congregational Association's ownership of properties such as the Somerset Building and the Congregational House at 14 Beacon Street, Boston, Massachusetts. This subseries contains deeds and quitclaim deeds, ledgers, and records relating to financing and capital funding.
    - Deeds and mortgages, 1846 1896; 1846-1896 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Quitclaim deeds, 1866 1875; 1866-1875 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Mortgage and deeds, 1874 1897; 1874-1897 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Mortgage, 1896 1927; 1896-1927 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Deed, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Principle deed, 1896 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Quitclaim deeds, 1897 1900; 1897-1900 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Building ledger book, 1920 1926; 1920-1926 (Box 9, Volume 6)
    - Building insurance appraisal, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Bond financing, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Capital planning, 2012 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Assessments and reports, 1871 2019; 1871-2019; 26 Folders
    This subseries contains reports, assessments, and other memos related to the Congregational House at 14 Beacon Street, Boston, Massachusetts as well as the Somerset Building. Most of the records within this collection are related to the physical status of the building and many are related to assessments taken prior to construction or renovation projects.
    - Reports and deeds, 1871 1896; 1871-1896 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Architect's reports, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Real estate appaisals, 1922 1942; 1922-1942 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Building reports, 1924 1934; 1924-1934 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Building upkeep reports, 1927 1981; 1927-1981 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1931 1950; 1931-1950 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1951 1961; 1951-1961 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Superintendent's reports, 1962 1977; 1962-1977 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Alley accident and liability, 1934 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Environmental planning memos, 1996 1997; 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Massachusetts Historical Commission restoration grant final report, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Property condition report, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Infrastructure report, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 12)